A Guide to the Agricultural Development Council records, Record Group 1 FA078
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Research and Training Network, 1953-1977; 3
  - Research and Training Network - Grants, 3.3
    - Ohio State University - Agricultural Economics Summer Course, 1958-1959 (Box 21, Folder 291)
    - Ohio State University - Agricultural Economics Summer Course, 1958-1959 (Box 21, Folder 292)
    - Ohio State University - Agricultural Economics Summer Course, 1958-1959 (Box 21, Folder 293)
    - Ohio State University - Agricultural Economics Summer Course, 1958-1959 (Box 21, Folder 294)
    - Ohio State University - Agricultural Economics Summer Course, 1958-1959 (Box 22, Folder 295)
    - Ohio State University - Agricultural Economics Summer Course, 1958-1959 (Box 22, Folder 296)
    - Oommen, M. A. - Travel, 1969-1972 (Box 22, Folder 297)
    - Oregon State University - Summer Session Graduate Course, 1962-1964 (Box 22, Folder 298)
    - Padjadjaran University - Soewardi, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 299)
    - Pantjasila Farmers' Union - Publication, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 300)
    - Pak, Ki Hyuk - Travel, 1964, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 301)
    - Pak, Ki Hyuk - Travel, 1964, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 302)
    - Park, Tai Sik - Travel, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 303)
    - Paulino, Leonardo - Travel, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 304)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Comparative Studies, 1959-1960 (Box 22, Folder 305)
    - University of the Philippines - Agricultural Credit and Cooperatives Institute, 1958-1961 (Box 22, Folder 306)
    - University of the Philippines - Agricultural Economics Building Wing, 1958-1959 (Box 22, Folder 307)
    - University of the Philippines - Chungtes Study, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 308)
    - University of the Philippines - College of Forestry - Conservation Study, 1968-1971 (Box 22, Folder 309)
    - University of the Philippines - Community Development Research Council - Casino Study, 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 310)
    - University of the Philippines - Community Development Research Council - Chan Study, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 311)
    - University of the Philippines - Community Development Research Council - Guerrero Project, 1964-1966 (Box 23, Folder 312)
    - University of the Philippines - Community Development Research Council - Highway Access Project, 1963-1964 (Box 23, Folder 313)
    - University of the Philippines - Community Development Research Council - Salim, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder 314)
    - University of the Philippines - Community Development Research Council - Barrio Development, 1963, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 315)
    - University of the Philippines - Cooperation Among Agricultural Colleges, 1964-1965 (Box 23, Folder 316)
    - University of the Philippines - Cooperation Price Study, 1960-1962 (Box 23, Folder 317)
    - University of the Philippines - Experimental Radio Station at Los Banos, 1963-1695 (Box 23, Folder 318)
    - University of the Philippines - Farm Management Study in Southern Luzon, 1958-1964 (Box 23, Folder 319)
    - University of the Philippines - Farm Management Study in Southern Luzon, 1958-1964 (Box 23, Folder 320)
    - University of the Philippines - Home Technology Agents for Farm Development Teams, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 321)
    - University of the Philippines - House Construction at Los Banos, 1963-1965 (Box 23, Folder 322)
    - University of the Philippines - Husband/Wife Role's Among Professionals, 1964-1965 (Box 23, Folder 323)
    - University of the Philippines - In-Service Training Conferences, 1960-1961 (Box 23, Folder 324)
    - University of the Philippines - Institute of Mass Communications - Farmers Expectations, 1967-1970 (Box 23, Folder 325)
    - University of the Philippines - Institute of Mass Communications - Impact of, 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 326)
    - University of the Philippines - Institute of Mass Communications - Relative Effect, 1967-1970 (Box 24, Folder 327)
    - University of the Philippines - Kaingin Agriculture Study, 1961-1962 (Box 24, Folder 328)
    - University of the Philippines - Landlord Study Supplement, 1969-1970 (Box 24, Folder 329)
    - University of the Philippines - Preparation and Testing of Teaching Materials, 1957-1959 (Box 24, Folder 330)
    - University of the Philippines - Ramachandran, 1966-1969 (Box 24, Folder 331)
    - University of the Philippines - Role of Landlord in Agricultural Development, 1964-1968 (Box 24, Folder 332)
    - University of the Philippines - Role of the Landlord, 1967-1969 (Box 24, Folder 333)
    - University of the Philippines - Student Manual - Vocational Agriculture (Box 24, Folder 334)
    - University of the Philippines - Student Manual - Vocational Agriculture (Box 24, Folder 335)
    - University of the Philippines - Studies on Land Classification and Landless Agricultural Laborers, 1962-1966 (Box 24, Folder 336)
    - University of the Philippines - Tablante Consultancy, 1962-1963 (Box 24, Folder 337)
    - University of the Philippines - Villanueva - Rural Poverty Productivity Survey, 1958-1966 (Box 25, Folder 338)
    - University of the Philippines - Visayan Village Life Study, 1964-1966 (Box 25, Folder 339)
    - University of Pittsburgh - Manalang Dissertation, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 340)
    - Ranchi Agricultural College, 1961-1963 (Box 25, Folder 341)
    - Ray - Land Tenure Study, 1955-1957 (Box 25, Folder 342)
    - Raza - Travel, 1962-1963 (Box 25, Folder 343)
    - University of Reading - International Seminar on Change in Agriculture, 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 344)
    - Rhee - Travel, 1964-1965 (Box 25, Folder 345)
    - College of Rural Higher Education - Small Farmer's Credit, 1969-1972 (Box 25, Folder 346)
    - Rural Home Life Improvement Study Society, Inc., 1957-1959 (Box 25, Folder 347)
    - Rural Home Life Improvement Study Society, Inc., 1957-1959 (Box 25, Folder 348)
    - Rural Sociology Congress - Travel, 1970-1972 (Box 25, Folder 349)
    - Rural Sociology Congress - Travel, 1970-1972 (Box 25, Folder 350)
    - Rural Sociology, 2nd World Congress, 1967-1968 (Box 26, Folder 351)
    - Rural Sociology, 2nd World Congress, 1967-1968 (Box 26, Folder 352)
    - Sahertian-Bakoven, Pauline, 1964-1967 (Box 26, Folder 353)
    - Sta. Iglesia, Jesus - Travel, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 354)
    - Sawada, Shujiro - Travel, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 355)
    - Seoul National University - Analysis of IR667 Cultivation, 1972-1975 (Box 26, Folder 356)
    - Seoul National University - Ban, S. H. - Farm Resources, 1963-1966 (Box 26, Folder 357)
    - Seoul National University - Bratton - Training Center on Farm Management Analysis, 1963-1964 (Box 26, Folder 358)
    - Seoul National University - Cho - Publications of Teaching Materials, 1958-1960 (Box 26, Folder 359)
    - Seoul National University - Influence of Weather on Crop Production, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 360)
    - Seoul National University - Kim - Cooperative Farms in Reclaimed Mountain Lands, 1963-1967 (Box 26, Folder 361)
    - Seoul National University - Park - Rice Yield Sampling Methods, 1962-1963, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 362)
    - Seoul National University - Park - Farm Management Study, 1963-1966 (Box 27, Folder 363)
    - Seoul National University - Seminar on Korean Agricultural Development, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 364)
    - Seoul National University - Shim - Marketing of Rice in the Suwon Area, 1965-1968 (Box 27, Folder 365)
    - Seoul National University - Southworth - National Summer Course in Agricultural Marketing Research, 1965-1966 (Box 27, Folder 366)
    - Seoul National University - Wang - Adoption of Farming and Homemaking Practices in Nucleated Villages, 1962-1963, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 367)
    - Seoul National University - Wang Project - Sociological Analysis of Rice Cultivation Practice, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 368)
    - Sharma, J. N., 1969-1971 (Box 27, Folder 369)
    - Shiga Agricultural College - Sakurai, 1959-1962 (Box 27, Folder 370)
    - Shim, Young Kim - Travel, 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder 371)
    - Sibulo, Vincente - Travel, 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder 372)
    - Sopin, Tongpan - Travel, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 373)
    - Silliman University - Agricultural Economics Studies in Negros Oriental, 1958-1959 (Box 27, Folder 374)
    - Silliman University - Community Arts Program, 1957-1960 (Box 28, Folder 375)
    - Silliman University - Community Development Program Evaluation, 1957-1960 (Box 28, Folder 376)
    - Silliman University - Farm Management Survey in Negros Oriental, 1957-1960 (Box 28, Folder 377)
    - Silliman University - Farm Management Survey in Negros Oriental, 1957-1960 (Box 28, Folder 378)
    - Silliman University - Radio Program within Community Development Program, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 379)
    - Sinaga, Rudolf, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 380)
    - Singapore University - Tan, 1968-1971 (Box 28, Folder 381)
    - Singh, A. S. - Travel, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 382)
    - Soberano, Jose - Travel, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 383)
    - Society for International Development, 1961-1963 (Box 28, Folder 384)
    - Soeharjo - Study and Consultation at Los Banos, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 385)
    - Song, Y. S. - Travel, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 386)
    - Southeast Asian Geographers Regional Conference, 1961-1962 (Box 28, Folder 387)
    - Southern Illinois University - Orientation Program for Foreign Graduate Students, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 388)
    - Srinivasan, M. - Travel, 1968-1971 (Box 28, Folder 389)
    - Sudarsono, Hadisapoetro - Travel, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 390)
    - Suh, Joong Il - Travel, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 391)
    - Sung, Bai Yung - Travel, 1970, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 392)
    - Sung, M. N. - Travel, 1966-1968 (Box 29, Folder 393)
    - University of Sussex - Institute of Development Studies - Social Prerequisites for Agricultural Cooperation, 1967-1970 (Box 29, Folder 394)
    - Taiwan Provincial Chung Hsing University - Economic Study of Land Use in Taichung Area, 1960-1965 (Box 29, Folder 395)
    - Taiwan Provincial Chung Hsing University - Economic Study of Land Use in Taichung Area, 1960-1965 (Box 29, Folder 396)
    - Taiwan Provincial Chung Hsing University - Lee - Land Use Classification in Ancient China, 1963-1966 (Box 29, Folder 397)
    - Taiwan Provincial Chung Hsing University - Wu, M. W. - Travel, 1966-1968 (Box 29, Folder 398)
    - Taiwan Provincial College of Agriculture - Graduate Tour, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 399)
    - Takahashi, Iichiro - Publication, 1960-1965 (Box 29, Folder 400)
    - Texas A & M College - Visitors from Ceylon, 1961-1964 (Box 29, Folder 401)
    - Thailand - Ministry of Agriculture - Farm Management Training Center, 1959-1960 (Box 29, Folder 402)
    - Thailand - Kasetsart University Farm Management Students, 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 403)
    - Thailand - Ministry of Agriculture - In-Service Training Program, 1970-1973 (Box 30, Folder 404)
    - Thailand - Ministry of Agriculture - In-Service Training Program, 1970-1973 (Box 30, Folder 405)
    - Ting, W. P. - Travel, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 406)
    - Tiongson, Fabian - Travel, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 407)
    - Tojib, Hadiwidjaja - Travel, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 408)
    - Tottori University - Coordinating Farm Management Research with Farm Management Extension Program, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 409)
    - Tottori University - Economics of Dairy Farming, 1959-1961 (Box 30, Folder 410)
    - Tuan, Chyau - Travel, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 411)
    - Wallach, I. - American Films in Japan, 1953-1958 (Box 30, Folder 412)
    - Wang, In Keun - Travel, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 413)
    - State College of Washington - Survey of Patwari, 1957-1960 (Box 30, Folder 414)
    - Watanabe, Tadashi - Publication, 1963-1964 (Box 30, Folder 415)
    - Wong, Chen-ta - Travel, 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 416)
    - Wood, G. B. - Asian Study Trip, 1960-1961 (Box 30, Folder 417)
    - Yang, Martin M. C. - Travel, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 418)
    - Yeoh, Oon Lee - Travel, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 419)
    - Yoo, Kang Hee - Travel, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 420)
    - Yoon, Hyo Jik - Travel, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 421)
  - Research and Training Network - Publications, 3.5
    - Newsletter, Nos. 1-8, 1971-1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Reprint, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Seminar Report, 1972-1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Workshop Report, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Training Materials Project, 1958-1967; 4
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  The Training Materials Project series includes material especially pertaining to the volume "Getting Agriculture Moving" and its supplementary volumes.
  - General (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Advisory Committee (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - "Agricultural Development" (pre-"Getting Agriculture Moving"), 1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - American Association of Agricultural College Editors - Borton - Committee (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bibliographies, Indexed (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bibliographies, Indexed (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Book Lists (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Case Studies (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Case Studies - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Case Studies - Author Permissions, Nos. 1-15 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence - Fort, 1964 (Box 1A, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Fort, 1964 (Box 1A, Folder 2)
  - Case Studies - Author Permissions, Nos. 16-31 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Case Studies - Author Permissions, Nos. 32-53 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Charts and Maps (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Classification (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Classification Materials (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Consultant - Collins, Peter B. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Conferences - Asia, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Copyright (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence (A-B), 1964 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence (C-G), 1964 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence (H-L), 1964 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence (M-R), 1964 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence (S-Y), 1964 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence (A-B), 1965 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence (C-E), 1965 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence (F-I), 1965 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence (J-L), 1965 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence (M-O), 1965 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence (P-S), 1965 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence (T-Z), 1965 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence (A-C), 1966 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence (D-H), 1966 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence (I-O), 1966 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence (P-W), 1966 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence - Evans (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence - Ford Foundation (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence - Holmes - Etawah Paper (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence - Peace Corps (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence - Print (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence - Reisner, John (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Creating a Progressive Rural Structure - A. M. Mosher, July 1968 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Distribution (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Food and Agriculture Organization - Farm Management Manual - Shipment (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Ford Foundation (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - "Getting Agriculture Moving" - Photocopy Edition with Notes, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - "Getting Agriculture Moving" - Paperback Edition (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - "Getting Agriculture Moving" - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - "Getting Agriculture Moving" - Correspondence (A-N), 1966 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - "Getting Agriculture Moving" - Correspondence (P-Y), 1966 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - "Getting Agriculture Moving" - Correspondence (A-O), 1967 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - "Getting Agriculture Moving" - Correspondence (P-Y), 1967 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - "Getting Agriculture Moving" - Correspondence - Packet (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - "Getting Agriculture Moving" - Correspondence - Production (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - "Getting Agriculture Moving" - Criticism (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - "Getting Agriculture Moving" - Draft - Mosher (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - "Getting Agriculture Moving" - Praeger (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - "Getting Agriculture Moving" - Promotion (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - "Getting Agriculture Moving" - Resume - Draft (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - "Getting Agriculture Moving" - Review (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - "Getting Agriculture Moving" - Selected Readings - Permissions (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - "Getting Agriculture Moving" - Portuguese Edition (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - "Getting Agriculture Moving" - Spanish Edition (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - "Getting Agriculture Moving" - Training Manual for Group Study - Mosher, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - "Getting Agriculture Moving" - Training Manual for Group Study - Draft (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Griffiths, V. L. (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Holmes, H. C. - Trip Notes - Africa, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Illustrations (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Insights (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Insights (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - "Insights to Agricultural Development" (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Kaufman-Singh Special Project (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Kaufman-Singh Special Project (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Latin America Trip Folder (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Memos, 1963-1966 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Memos, 1963-1966 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Memos, 1963-1966 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Memos, 1963-1966 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Memos, 1963-1966 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - "No Pone Valley" - Draft - Holmes (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Notes (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Packets (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Pay Orders (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - Posters (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Preliminary Programming - F. F. Hill (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Procedures and Notes (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - "Promoting Agricultural Growth" - Mosher - Draft, August 1967 (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - Quotations (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - Readings - Cards - Nos. 1-80 (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - Readings - Cards - Nos. 82-149 (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - Readings - Cards - Nos. 150-238 (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - Readings - Cards - Nos. 241-597 (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - Readings - Cards - Nos. 600's (Box 11, Folder 94)
  - Readings - Cards - Nos. 700's (Box 11, Folder 95)
  - Readings - Cards - Nos. 801-875 (Box 11, Folder 96)
  - Readings - Cards - Nos. 876-982 (Box 11, Folder 97)
  - Readings - Cards - Nos. 1033-1128 (Box 11, Folder 98)
  - Readings - Cards - Nos. 1136-1291 (Box 12, Folder 99)
  - Readings - Cards - Nos. 1304-1400 (Box 12, Folder 100)
  - Readings - Cards - Nos. 1405-1485 (Box 12, Folder 101)
  - Readings - Cards - Nos. 1486-1545 (Box 12, Folder 102)
  - Readings - Cards - Nos. 1546-1590 (Box 12, Folder 103)
  - Readings - Cards - Nos. 1600's (Box 12, Folder 104)
  - Readings - Cards - Nos. 1700's (Box 12, Folder 105)
  - Readings - Cards - Nos. 1800's (Box 12, Folder 106)
  - Readings - Cards - Nos. 1900's (Box 13, Folder 107)
  - Readings - Notes (Box 13, Folder 108)
  - Reports - Sponsored Agricultural Economics, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 109)
  - Reports - Final (Box 13, Folder 110)
  - Reprints for Discussion at Seminars - Nos. 23-849 (Box 13, Folder 111)
  - Reprints for Discussion at Seminars - Nos. 903-1387 (Box 13, Folder 112)
  - Reprints for Discussion at Seminars - Nos. 1430-1828 (Box 13, Folder 113)
  - Schickele, R. W. (Box 13, Folder 114)
  - Schickele, R. W. (Box 14, Folder 115)
  - Seminar - East African (Box 14, Folder 116)
  - Seminar - Philippines (Box 14, Folder 117)
  - Seminar - West African (Box 14, Folder 118)
  - Seminar - West African (Box 14, Folder 119)
  - Seminar - West African (Box 14, Folder 120)
  - Suggestions and Bibliographies (Box 14, Folder 121)
  - Vignettes (Box 14, Folder 122)
  - Miscellany (Box 14, Folder 123)
  - Miscellaneous Drafts (Box 14, Folder 124)
- Agricultural Development Council Annual Reports, 1963-1976, 1979-1980; 5; 14 Bound Volumes
  Arrangement
  Chronological
  Annual Reports also in Series 1: General, Subseries 6: Publications.
  Annual reports
  - ADC Annual Report 1963 (Item REF 630.7 AGI 1963)
  - ADC Annual Report 1964-1965 (Item REF 630.7 AGI 1964-65)
  - ADC Annual Report 1966 (Item REF 630.7 AGI 1966)
  - ADC Annual Report 1967 (Item REF 630.7 AGI 1967)
  - ADC Annual Report 1968 (Item REF 630.7 AGI 1968)
  - ADC Annual Report 1969-1970 (Item REF 630.7 AGI)
  - ADC Annual Report 1971 (Item REF 630.7 AGI 1971)
  - ADC Annual Report 1972 (Item REF 630.7 AGI 1972)
  - ADC Annual Report 1973 (Item REF 630.7 AGI 1973)
  - ADC Annual Report 1974 (Item REF 630.7 AGI 1974)
  - ADC Annual Report 1975 (Item REF 630.7 AGI 1975)
  - ADC Annual Report 1976 (Item REF 630.7 AGI 1976)
  - ADC Annual Report 1979 (Item REF 630.7 AGI 1979)
  - ADC Annual Report 1980 (Item REF 630.7 AGI 1980)
- Agricultural Development Council photographs, 1959-1971; 1032
  Photographs
  - Board of Trustees (Box 12, Folder 117)
  - Agricultural Economics Teaching, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 118)
  - Bicol Seminar, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 119)
  - Staff Conferences - Bali, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 120)
  - Book and Equipment Grants (Box 12, Folder 121)
  - Personnel (Box 12, Folder 122)
  - AURP - General (Box 12, Folder 123)
  - Geography and Agricultural Development, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 124)
  - Historical Studies, 1964 November 22-24 (Box 12, Folder 125)
  - Content of Education for Accelerated, 1965 January 29-31 (Box 12, Folder 126)
  - Restructuring Agricultural Curricula, 1965 March 7-8 (Box 12, Folder 127)
  - Labor Surplus and Dual Economy Model, 1965 May 29-30 (Box 12, Folder 128)
  - Role of Transportation, 1965 September 12-14 (Box 12, Folder 129)
  - Institutional Structures and Cultural ..., 1965 October 28-30 (Box 12, Folder 130)
  - Influence of Primary Exports..., 1965 November 20-21 (Box 12, Folder 131)
  - Research Implications of Recent..., 1966 March 11-13 (Box 12, Folder 132)
  - Purchased Inputs..., 1966 March 14-15 (Box 12, Folder 133)
  - Economic Apsects of the Operation..., 1966 April 22-24 (Box 12, Folder 134)
  - Planning Agricultural Development, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 135)
  - Latin America - Agricultural Development, 1967 July 25-27 (Box 12, Folder 136)
  - Trianing for Rural Sociologists, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 137)
  - Core Economics, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 138)
  - Problems of Teaching and Research in Farm..., 1968 January 16-18 (Box 12, Folder 139)
  - A Systems Analysis of Improved..., 1968 March 8-10 (Box 12, Folder 140)
  - Peasant Motivation and Economic Behavior, 1968 April 23-24 (Box 13, Folder 141)
  - Research on Economy of Agriculture..., 1968 June 9-14 (Box 13, Folder 142)
  - University of Dacca (Box 13, Folder 143)
  - FAO (Box 13, Folder 144)
  - Hokkaido University, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 145)
  - India International Center (Box 13, Folder 146)
  - University of Indonesia (Box 13, Folder 147)
  - Institute Pertanian Bogor (Box 13, Folder 148)
  - Institute of International Education (Box 13, Folder 149)
  - ICAE (Box 13, Folder 150)
  - Kim, Hi Soon (Box 13, Folder 151)
  - Korea - FAO Association, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 152)
  - Kyoto University (Box 13, Folder 153)
  - University of Malaya (Box 13, Folder 154)
  - University of Minnesota (Box 13, Folder 155)
  - Ohio State University (Box 13, Folder 156)
  - University of Philippines (Box 13, Folder 157)
  - Rural Home Life Improvement Study Society, Inc. (Box 13, Folder 158)
  - Seoul National University, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 159)
  - Silliman University, Philippines (Box 13, Folder 160)
  - Thailand, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 161)
  - State College of Washington (Box 13, Folder 162)
  - FAO Seminar - Role of Asian Agricultural University in Small Farm Development (Box 13, Folder 163)
  - Hokkaido University (Box 13, Folder 164)
  - Household Budget Studies (Box 13, Folder 165)
  - Indian Society of Agricultural Economists (Box 13, Folder 166)
  - Kyoto University (Box 13, Folder 167)
  - Kyushu University (Box 13, Folder 168)
  - University of Mayala (Box 13, Folder 169)
  - Marketing Institutions and Services (Box 13, Folder 170)
  - University of Philippines (Box 13, Folder 171)
  - University of Philippines - Conference, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 172)
  - University of Philippines - Farm Development Project (Box 13, Folder 173)
  - Rubber Survey (1st, 2nd, 3rd) (Box 13, Folder 174)